Music
Thank you for watching
Okay, what is your name?
My name is Ryuta Nagano.
How did you come up with your name?
It's written "shinogu" and "big".
It means to endure all kinds of hardships and to be a big man.
I want you to be a big man.
That's why I got two hands.
What do people call you?
Ryota, Ryouchin, Nagano and Oi.
Hey?
Where are you from?
I'm from Shizuoka.
I was born in Shizuoka and grew up in Tokyo.
I was born in Shizuoka.
What is your birthday?
My birthday is July 16th.
It is the day of the seven colors.
What is your blood type?
My blood type is A.
What is your favorite part of your face?
My eyes.
They are brown.
What are your hobbies?
I have many hobbies.
I like to look for clothes.
I like listening to music and playing music.
I also like to play games and read books.
Patents?
My patent is called "Mouth Mushroom".
It's a way of expressing mushrooms with my mouth.
It's the only thing that's kept me alive in the entertainment industry.
Here we go.
See you in the next video.
That's all.
Do something funny.
Something funny?
What's funny?
Pudding.
What's your favorite food?
Lately, I've been eating natto and...
And cheese.
I like cheese like yogurt.
I don't like
Anko (red bean paste)
I don't like it.
My favorite color is
Blue, white and
black
Lately I like pink.
My strength is
Never give up
My weakness is stubbornness.
I'm stubborn.
To bend too much.
I'm always saying.
I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure.
I agree with everything.
My charm point is
I'm friendly.
I don't think so.
I don't know.
What do you want to fix?
I'm too nervous.
No matter what I do.
I get nervous about everything.
I want to fix it.
I'm not good at...
I haven't seen the members in a while.
We laughed so much.
You know...
I sweat a lot.
I'm a sweaty person.
My daily routine is
Strength training and drinking lots of water
Drink lots of it.
If you could have one thing on a deserted island, what would it be?
Something
Something I can fight with
A sword
Is
If you could climax.
What do you think?
I'd like to...
I'd like to go back and forth between eras.
A lottery ticket?
Uh, but maybe some clothes or self-improvement.
What do you think? What's the target method?
Buy a lot of stuff.
What's your treasure?
Well... it's a group.
And observers.
Oldest memory? Oh, you mean an old memory.
I don't know.
I don't know... being bathed... when I was a little girl.
Air guitar, please.
Air guitar?
Chitty-chitty-chitty-chitty!
Ding!
What's the gentlest thing you've ever played?
Who's the nicest?
Uh, Joon-kun.
I think everyone calls him Jun-kun.
Are you too strict?
Me or Taka?
Unexpected side of you?
Uh...
He seems confident, but he's actually very nervous.
Poker face...
Kaname and Jun. Who do you think you are in the club?
I'm the one who relieves everyone's stress.
One secret about myself that even the members don't know... I'm not so much a surprise... I mean, I'm really good with my legs.
What is the one thing you can't lose to anyone?
Oh, but it's my passion for music. I want to keep doing it no matter what.
Is there anyone you would like to meet? There are many, but I've always admired Halloween Hosono.
And of course, Tamori-san. My boom... cafes! I spend all day in cafes.
How do you spend your day at the back of the house? There is a place where you can pay to stay all day.
I often go there.
I like to go to places where I can do things I enjoy during the show.
Watching videos, youtube and movies at home makes me sleepy.
It was totally different from now. It was more outdoorsy and cheerful.
Who is your favorite comedian? I like Rainbow and Metal Butt.
Death? Death?
If the balloons were to merge tomorrow? If a balloon went hot tomorrow, what would you do?
If a balloon went hot tomorrow, what would you do?
I'd like to go to a live concert.
If I were reincarnated, I would be a cat
If you could write one kanji character to describe yourself, what would it be?
War.
I feel like I'm fighting.
Where would you like to travel?
America
Do you easily forget bad things? Do you drag it out?
I drag it out a lot.
What is your fetish?
Fetish?
The smell of leather seats when I enter a car.
Here's a question from the observers.
Oh, I have one of those.
What is your favorite outfit?
Suddenly it's difficult.
But the glasses at the encore of Ingaris' inverted arena live show.
I was very happy because I usually like glasses myself!
Onigiri (rice ball)
I just ate a sea chicken!
What do you value?
What I value is to never bend myself and to achieve everything I want to do.
What is your favorite phrase from your part?
Let's go to Tomo in Museum Zero and let's go to Towa in Museum Zero... I think these are the words I want to convey the most to the observers in Museum Zero.
What was your favorite event in the gymnastics festival?
The relay.
Reward yourself?
A week of unlimited access to festivals.
Favorite food to eat?
It's hard.
I like "android" and "Mr.android".
What do you want to eat now?
Ramen noodles
I haven't eaten ramen for a long time.
If you had 7 days off, what would you do?
I would travel.
I'd like to go to America, Korea, France, etc.
If seven people were your family, what would your family consist of?
What? What if you and Taka were a family?
What? What if Taka is the family first?
What? What if Taka is your family first?
Mom...
And Kaname is the dad.
Jun is my brother.
And I'm next.
Kazuto and Kousaku are my cousins.
Cousins who are like mean brothers
Naughty brothers
And Masaya is one step younger than me.
Where do you like to sit in the classroom?
Uh, the very end, by the window.
Right by the window, right by the window!
By the window! Second to the front of the window, or the very back.
Composition in the local club
Local club?
Yeah, full of energy.
They grew up so well.
Uh, Genji, you're proud of your children?
Eh, Genji, proud of our children?
Eh, buh-buh-buh? Ehh, buh-buh, we have fun live like a trapeze artist.
If you were to compare the members to an oden nugui, what would it be?
Takato is a purse and Kousaku is a daikon radish.
Masaya, huh?
Masaya, hanbe.
Chikuwa is Kaname.
Jun is an egg
And Kazuto, shirataki.
I'll have shiru-bee then.
Okay, dashi.
What color would Jun's side be if it were curry ralul?
Wow, white.
What was your favorite picture book?
Uh, Who's the Missing Child?
What's the Missing Persons Bar?
The one with the ghosts.
It's a dress-up version of my line.
Who's the girl who won't sleep?
Who's the girl who won't sleep? Who's the girl who won't sleep?
What do you think is the charm of the local club?
Well, it's full of members' personalities.
And the music is unique.
Which songs do you enjoy singing in the local group?
Oh, I'd have to say "Illusion of Zeros and Ones".
Cat of a dog, and so on.
Describe your favorite emoji with your face.
Oh, I have this one.
I've got this one.
It's a good one.
I often use it on Instagram.
Today's breakfast is natto and yogurt.
Do you usually eat breakfast properly? Breakfast
I eat breakfast.
What is the most relaxing time of the day?
On my way home.
I feel most relaxed when I'm walking home after a day's work.
Rehearsal?
Towels. I sweat a lot.
If you weren't acting or playing music, what would you be doing?
Wow, that's hard to say. I don't know what I would be doing.
I'm an office worker, I guess.
What has been an inspirational episode recently?
I knew it was Masaya in the arena.
Suddenly, he was singing in a way I've never seen him do before.
I could feel that he was adjusting to it so well.
It made me want to work harder on my singing and dancing.
If you were an animal, what would you be?
I'm sure people would say a dog.
I'd like a cat.
A cat or a fox.
If you could switch places for a day, who would you be?
Anybody but me.
I'm Yazawa of the world.
I'm Eiki Yazawa of the world.
Eiki Yazawa.
I'd come in a few minutes before the show.
He'd come in a few minutes before the show, put on his gown, and leave.
I thought, "I want to go home.
Where else but Japan would you come and perform?
Definitely the U.S.A.
The Drapals in America.
Or Coach.
I'd love to play festivals.
That's my dream.
Who do you admire?
Uh, yeah.
But lately I've been admiring Berry Iris.
What do you want to see?
Let's see...
Leon.
The famous
I've always wanted to see it.
I don't know...
I've never seen it properly.
I don't like to watch it intermittently.
I'd like to take a picture of the one I want to see properly for two hours.
I'd like to watch them when I have time.
What is the point of choosing clothes?
I'm thinking about what I want to wear when I'm on stage as a solo artist.
If I were to go on stage as a solo performer, which one would I want to use as my costume?
What kind of bread do you buy at the bakery?
Let's see... French bread.
The croissant?
Is there a difference between a croissant and French bread?
Not at all.
French bread?
Yes, yes.
Oh, definitely not.
I would never buy that.
Croissant.
Appealing point.
Well, I don't know...
It has many aspects.
Such as?
Well, I feel like I'm often described as having a gap between my personality and that of others.
I'm often said to be quiet when I'm at a concert or in a photo.
But I'm surprisingly talkative and energetic to those who are comfortable with me.
So I guess I have many sides to me.
A good thing that happened this week?
Well, I don't know.
Well, for me, it's been getting colder recently, and I like winter, so that's been a good thing.
Oh, and I bought new shoes.
You know that pass I had the other day?
I was very happy when the balance on it reached zero.
What keeps you going?
Observers.
What is your favorite side dish?
My favorite side dish is croquette.
What song do you think of when you think of yourself?
Uh...
Well, it's all about me, isn't it?
I've been working on this song since the first time I performed it on stage.
That's probably how I got to where I am today.
Previous life?
My previous life must have been that one.
Employee
I think my father.
What would you like for the last supper of your life?
Wow, this is a tough one.
It's either oyakodon, which my grandma made, or sushi, which is really good!
Which seat on the bullet train do you like?
Uh, yeah, the window seat.
I think I really like the window best.
I think it's my favorite. It's a window seat for three.
Where would you most like to go now?
America, I've been going there for a long time.
Korea... Kyoto... Kyoto...
I'd like to go there.
What foreign words have you learned recently?
Recently learned
I recently learned Off Course.
I've known this for a long time.
What is the picture of your wallet?
It's unique.
What's your favorite picture you've taken recently?
Well, this one.
There's a cat on the road that I often walk on.
There is a cat on the road that I often walk on, or rather, on the flat road I walk on.
And I don't have a cat.
I didn't have a cat, but there was a black cat that I wanted to have someday.
He didn't look at me at all.
But I took a picture of its back.
Here it is.
When do you feel happy in winter?
When I'm rushing home in the cold.
I think it's romantic.
And Christmas.
The city makes me happy.
I can think of a lot of four-letter words.
It's a four-letter word, isn't it?
"I," "blonde," and "me.
Yes, sir.
What sport are you good at?
I played soccer from kindergarten to junior high school.
I also like to say I'm good at basketball.
What is the most impressive dream you had while sleeping?
I was dancing on stage and I was so scared that I forgot everything and just stood there.
When I was a little boy, my dream was to be a train conductor, because I loved trains so much.
I wanted to be a train conductor and a soccer player.
Coffee? Tea?
Uh, coffee.
Favorite doughnut?
Uh, plain.
What's plain?
It's some kind of sugar.
What's your favorite dish?
My specialty is making omelet eggs.
It doesn't look good, but...
But it tastes good.
What do you want to try most?
My biggest challenge is to start skateboarding.
I want to make my own skateboard.
I want to put a lot of stickers on it and move around by skateboard.
What would you like people to listen to most?
Museum Zero, because it's the newest song.
Museum Zero and Winter
Snow Dance.
What do you want to do this year?
I'm torn.
What is it?
I'd like to peel off my skin.
I don't know.
Any last words?
Thank you very much.
See you soon!